[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "alt": "Nike Air Force 1 Black Shoe",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Air Force 1",
    "color": "Black",
    "price": "100.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-black-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-black-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-black-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "alt": "Nike Air Force 1 White Shoe",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Air Force 1",
    "color": "White",
    "price": "100.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-white-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-white-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-force-1-white-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "alt": "Nike Dunk Low Green Shoe",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Dunk Low",
    "color": "Green",
    "price": "90.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-green-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-green-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-green-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "alt": "Nike Dunk Low Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Dunk Low",
    "color": "Orange/Black",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-orangeblack-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-orangeblack-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/dunk-low-orangeblack-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "alt": "Nike Blazer Low 77 Jumbo Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Blazer Low 77 Jumbo",
    "color": "White",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/blazer-low-77-jumbo-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/blazer-low-77-jumbo-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/blazer-low-77-jumbo-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "alt": "Nike Air Max 1 Grey Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Air Max 1",
    "color": "Grey",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-grey-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-grey-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-grey-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "alt": "Nike Air Max 1 White and Black Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Air Max 1",
    "color": "White/Black",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-whiteblack-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-whiteblack-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/air-max-1-whiteblack-3.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "alt": "Nike Vomero 5 Black Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Vomero 5",
    "color": "Black",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-black-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-black-1.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-black-1.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "alt": "Nike Vomero 5 White Shoes",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "Vomero 5",
    "color": "White",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-white-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-white-1.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/zoom-vomero-5-white-1.webp"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "alt": "Nike V2K White Shoe",
    "brand": "Nike",
    "description": "V2K",
    "color": "White",
    "price": "120.00",
    "src": {
      "left": "src/assets/images/shoes/v2k-white-1.webp",
      "right": "src/assets/images/shoes/v2k-white-2.webp",
      "front": "src/assets/images/shoes/v2k-white-3.webp"
    }
  }
]
